They're dying to play with you.
Wild Things is a mystery, thriller, drama film directed by John McNaughton.
When teen-socialite Kelly Van Ryan and troubled bad girl Suzie Toller accuse guidance counselor Sam Lombardo of
rape, he's suspended by the school, rejected by the town, and fighting to get his life back.
One cop suspects conspiracy, but nothing is what it seems...
Sergeant Ray Duquette, played by Kevin Bacon.
Sam Lombardo, played by Matt Dillon.
Suzie Toller, played by Neve Campbell.
Kelly Van Ryan, played by Denise Richards.
Sandra Van Ryan, played by Theresa Russell.
Kenneth Bowden, played by Bill Murray.
Wild Things is a 1998 American erotic thriller film directed by John McNaughton and starring Matt Dillon,
Kevin Bacon, Neve Campbell, Denise Richards, Theresa Russell, Robert Wagner, and Bill Murray.
It follows a high school guidance counselor in South Florida who is accused of rape by two female students and a
series of subsequent revelations after a police officer begins investigating the alleged crimes.
Wild Things was released by Columbia Pictures on March 20, 1998 and received mixed to positive
reviews from critics while grossing $67.2 million against a $20 million budget.
The film was followed by three direct-to-DVD standalone sequels, namely Wild Things 2 (2004),
Wild Things: Diamonds in the Rough (2005), and Wild Things: Foursome (2010).
Since its release, the original film has been regarded as a cult classic.
The film explores themes of sailboat, florida, rape, sexual abuse, court case.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.